OSKAR DUDEK

Senior Full Stack Developer

@ leonablue2016@gmail.com

@ github.com/leonablue2016

Lublin, Poland

SUMMARY

Senior front-end web developer with 7+ years of experience coding websites that convert in e-commerce. Proficient with HTML, CSS, Shopify and GTM tag setup. Most notably, improved the average time on page by 40% and improved user experience scores for all projects. Winner of the Best Homepage Award by Shopify E-Commerce Design Awards in 2014.

EXPERIENCE

07/2021 - 02/2023

Senior Full Stack Developer

Boston, MA

Gutmann

Gutmann is a global services company that provides customers with access to products, insights and experiences that enrich lives and build business success.

- Developed 50 responsive websites for clients in a variety of industries
- Setup tracking with GTM and GA, integrated HTML/CSS into the CMS and conducted day-to-day maintenance of the websites, resulting in a combined \$40M of revenue for clients
- Collaborated with marketing and project management teams to deliver projects on-time and with the highest standard, retaining over 98% of clients in a 5-year period
- Performed full cycle recruiting, averaging 100+ interviews per month
- · Extensive and varied contributions to the company's internal backend framework with a team of 4+ developers

06/2017 - 03/2021

Web Developer

Singapore,

Sea Limited

Sea Limited is a multinational company headquartered in Singapore. It was founded in 2009 by Forrest Li and initially started as an online gaming company.

- · Increased by 35% the reach of users to the platform, over the installation of the web platform in mobile devices
- · Managed 7 outsourced web developers, designers and content writers
- Reduced daily data processing time by 77% by implementing stored procedures in the web portal used nationwide
- Overhauled the automated test framework for the web services, leading to about 90% reduction in debugging and issue resolution time

02/2014 - 12/2016

Junior Web Developer

Wroclaw, Poland

Divante

The company was founded in 2008 and is headquartered in Wroclaw, Poland, with additional offices in Krakow and Rzeszow

- · Created and maintained 10+ web applications for numerous national and foreign clients
- · Mobilized cross-platform testing on 4 different web browsers and 3 standalone applications in web and cloud base
- · Worked with over 15+ small scale web based projects and 2+ large scale web applications
- · Contributed to the development of over 10 web and mobile applications
- · Launched a company-wide digitized filing system that led to an increase in efficiency for all departments by 20% on average

EDUCATION

02/2012 - 07/2016

BSc in Web Development

Wroclaw, Poland

Wroclaw University

TECH STACK

Gitlab	Github	Bitbucket	SCSS	LESS	DNS Management	Nodejs	React Native	React Redux	Angular	
APIs	Wireframes Mongoose		se Cro	Cross-browser compatibility						